Now over this module, we did add a lot of forms and validation related functionality and I noticed a
imdi bu Marchal'da pek ok form ve dorulama ile ilgili ilevler ekledik ve bir hata
bug,
farkettim.
I'll be honest I noticed it after I recorded this module.
Drst olacam, bu modl kaydettikten sonra farkettim.
It's not a severe one,
Bu ciddi deil.
we're going to fix it later in this course. In our contact data container where we have the state managing
Bu dersin ilerleyen ksmlarnda, iletiim esi veri kapsaycmzda zeceiz. Setiimiz e
our form controls, delivery method, that's our select element right,
doru olan form kontrolleri datm yntemimizi ynetmek zorundayz.
and there I set a value of empty string initially.
Ve balangta bo bir dize deeri ayarladm.
Now we have the options, fastest or cheapest, an empty string doesn't make much sense,
imdi en hzl veya en ucuz iki seenek var, bo bir dize pek mantkl deil.
now on the UI we will see fastest and cheapest
imdi kullanc arayznde en hzl ve en ucuzu greceiz.
but if we never switch the option, behind the scenes value will always stay an empty string,
Fakat asla sahne arkasndaki seenei deitirmediysek, deer her zaman bo bir dize kalr.
it will always be updated once we trigger onChange,
Deiiklik zerine tetiklediimizde her zaman gncellenecektir.
so once we did change the value once. This will become an issue later when we submit our form to the
Dolaysyla, bir kez foruma sunucumuza gnderdiimizde bu durum bir kez daha deere dntrecek
server, then we will actually submit an empty value in case we never switch the value. Again,
ve daha sonra deeri tekrar deitirmememiz iin aslnda bo bir deer gndereceiz.
I will fix it later in the course
Bunu daha sonra kurda zeceim.
just in case you already noted it,
Durumunda sen zaten kaydetti.
good job.
Aferin.
Again will be fixed,
Tekrar dzeltilecek.
the fix is as easy as simply entering fastest or cheapest as the default here and you can choose which ever
Dzeltme, burada varsaylan olarak en hzl veya en ucuza girmek kadar kolay ve hangisini
one you want.
istediinizi seebilirsiniz.
So that is how to fix this,
Bunu dzeltmenin yolu budur.
again I'll leave it as we have it here, will be fixed later.
Tekrar buradan ayrlacam, burada dzeltileceim gibi.